Please bring me my word right in line.
Please bring it to me.
Shall we go in?
There's no way!
I'm not telling you!
It's true!
That's crazy!
I'm kidding!
Isn't this character over here look like someone else?
See it now?
Thanks!
Teacher!
The fly hit me on the back again!
It's nice to meet you.
You must be Kokuro.
My name is Mrs. Kitajima.
May I sit down?
According to our records, you're currently attending Yukishina Junior High School.
Is that right?
Yes.
I went there for Junior High too.
Oh.
Sometimes, I have this dream.
A transfer student shows up.
And they're talented and cool.
They notice me out of the whole class.
They come up to me.
And then, with a smile as warm as the sun,
they go,
Kokuro, long time no see.
Good to see you.
Everyone's breath is taken away.
I keep on wishing for something like that to happen.
But it won't come true.
It's just a fantasy.
All right.
I'm off.
Have a good day, sweetheart.
Hey, Mom.
My stomach's hurting.
Hurting how?
The same way it always does.
Can you describe it to me?
It just turns.
That means you're not going.
So you're staying home.
All right, then.
I can't.
Your eyes are undisturbed home.
I'm flying over.
No.
He is a thief who knows.
Good.
Maybe the entrepreneur?
It just turns.
That means you're not going.
So you're staying home.
All right, then.
I mean, I want to go, but I can't.
Uh, good morning to you as well.
I'm calling about my daughter, Kokoro Anzai.
I know it was supposed to be her first day, but unfortunately she's not feeling too well.
I'm not lying.
My stomach really does hurt.
I know it was supposed to be her day before her.
I'm not lying.
I's lying.
I'm lying.
I don't know.
It's Moe.
We've been waiting for you.
Wh-what?
A castle?
Yes! Congratulations!
You have been cordially invited as one of our honored guests.
Hold it!
Let me go home!
It's enough! Violence!
I can do this with six others today.
Frankly, I'm sick and tired of it.
You're the last one, and it's already 4 p.m.
Let's just get this over with.
Let go!
I don't care! Please let go of me!
Aren't you the least bit curious? That's a real castle.
Not to mention I'm exceedingly articulate and strong for my age.
You've stepped through the looking glass and into the pages of a fantasy novel.
Have you no sense of adventure?
I don't!
Even if your wish came true?
I suspect an ordinary girl like you must have something you'd like to wish for.
A wish?
Oh my god.
You must be petite.
Ah.
hard pain
Mmhmm.
The others await you.
Ah...
...
Hey, how's it going?
You sure kept us all waiting.
We heard that you'd be the last one to arrive, according to her.
I'm the Wolf Queen.
Okay, then the Wolf Queen told us.
She said that there needed to be seven of us here.
We've been waiting.
About an hour now.
So, um, what exactly is this place?
Why are we here?
Same story as us.
Our mirrors started glowing, and when we walked through, we were here.
I arrived here first.
The others appeared shortly after.
As for this place, we got a brief explanation, but honestly, I'm a little lost.
Huh?
You still don't get it?
Not really.
Me neither.
This is the last time I'll say it, so listen closely.
Somewhere in this castle is a small hidden room that cannot be entered.
The wishing room.
If you can find a way to get into that room, a wish will be granted.
However, there's a condition.
Only one out of the seven of you may enter.
My Little Red Riding Hoods.
She calls us that.
We're all lost Little Red Riding Hoods.
Hmm.
If you wish to enter into that room, you will need to have a key.
Starting today until March 30th of next year, you may search for the key hidden somewhere in this castle.
Only then do you ask in earnest for an ever-wish you desire.
Huh?
I don't get it.
Me neither.
I still have a lot of questions.
How exactly do you grant wishes?
What's with this key?
Why even bring us here?
Where even is here?
Enough!
No more questions!
Well, then you should have explained things better.
Why were we chosen in the first place?
You don't believe in dreams, do you?
Can't you all just appreciate that you're the stars of this story?
You even get your own room here in the castle!
So, rejoice!
You're the lucky ones.
You don't have to talk to us like that, you know.
For real.
Then tell me.
Your wish.
There must be something.
Ah.
Well, whether you have one or not, it's first come, first served.
Once someone finds the key and their wish is granted, it's game over.
The castle will close and the paths connected by the mirrors will disappear.
However, I'm not forcing you to search for the key while you're here.
Excuse me?
Does that mean we're allowed to come here anytime?
There are limits.
You can come from 9 to 5 p.m. Japan time.
9 to 5 p.m.?
Like, city hall?
Whatever you may think, this rule must absolutely be followed no matter what.
If you do not leave by 5 p.m., a wolf will eat you.
You'll eat us?
No, it's a real wolf.
It's frighteningly big.
If you don't believe me, see for yourself.
I promise you'll be eaten.
Also, even if only one among you breaks the rule, everyone in the castle that day will share the same fate.
You'll all be eaten.
Well, anyway, as long as you obey this one rule, you may come and go as freely as you please.
As we please, huh?
Uh-oh.
It's 4.30 already.
Tell me, did any of you look around the castle while you waited?
We did not have the time for a full tour today.
But it's a lot nicer than your homes, don't you think?
Girls, here.
Do you mind?
I'll be back shortly.
Why don't you introduce yourselves?
Oh, she's gone.
Is she a ghost?
I don't know.
I'll start.
My name is Aki, junior high.
Third year.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you as well.
Hi.
Hey there.
Hi, everyone.
Hmm.
My name is Kokoro.
I'm a first year.
It's very nice to meet you.
My name is Fuka.
Second year.
It's nice to meet all of you.
I'm Riyang.
First year.
Hello.
And my name is Subaru.
I'm a third year.
Hi.
Nice to meet you all.
Masamune.
Second year.
Oh.
Yeah, it's the same name as the famous general sword and sake brand.
And yes, it is my actual name.
So don't ask.
Urashina.
Which characters?
Well, it's actually my family name.
It's a combination of the characters for happy and for feel.
First year.
So we're all in junior high?
What's that?
I'm back.
That sound means it's 15 minutes to five.
Better leave or you'll be eaten.
Well, all right then.
Tell us how to get back home.
Look for your name.
Found it.
I haven't managed to get myself back to the castle.
I wonder if the others are there right now.
Okay.
You should come over sometime.
Really?
I will.
Wow, that red umbrella is so cute.
I think it suits you.
So, did you finish the homework?
Yeah.
Come on, let's go.
Figures you did.
That umbrella really is here.
There is one.
One thing that I wish would come true.
I'd do anything for it.
Come on!
Ah!
Damn it!
No luck, huh?
Ugh!
I keep dying every single time!
It'd be cool if we had a TV.
Then we could battle each other, Subaru.
No electricity.
Seriously, you two?
We're in a magical castle.
There's no need for a TV.
Says you.
What do you think this is?
Some kind of game?
There's no power to run it.
Could be manual.
Huh?
Sounds boring.
What are those?
Shogi puzzles?
Old school.
I think it's interesting.
Huh?
Come with one.
It's an amazingims Twice
on house.
What about you?
Huh?
That's so nice.
This is my life.
I think it's a hard time for you, you know.
What about you?
Love you too.
Time for you.
Good to you.
Hi, learning.
What?
Do we love you.
What about you?
I think it's beautiful.
You're a ghost witch?
I think it's a dream entre family,
right?
What about you?
You're a nightmare.
I don't know.
Oh, um, my name's Kokoro.
Yeah, I remember.
Headed back already?
Bye!
Hey, Kokoro!
You guys, Kokoro's here!
We waited for you.
Glad you made it back, Kokoro.
Long time.
Yo.
I, uh, I haven't had any time to visit.
Oh, okay.
We've all been coming quite a bit since that first time.
We mostly get together around this time in the afternoon.
Though I probably show up a little later in the day than all of you.
You're pretty early today.
I have practice.
Soccer.
But not today.
Someone else is coming.
Hmm?
Ah!
Good to see everyone!
Kokoro's here!
Now it's all seven of us.
I'll be in my room if you need me.
Wait!
Aki!
Where are you going?
I only just got here.
By the way, I brought some of my mom's special cookies for you to try.
They're really good.
Take a hint.
I can't watch.
I guess I missed out on things while I was gone.
But they were happy to see me.
I'll go again tomorrow.
Hey, Kokoro!
Huh?
Come, over here!
Boys are in there.
They're too annoying to deal with.
Though it's more Urashino than the other three.
Come down with us!
We spend a lot of our time in here.
And you can't beat that view.
Huh.
Check it out.
I found these beautiful teacups here.
But no running water to make tea.
Or a working stove.
So you have to bring your own drinks.
Here, have some.
Thank you very much.
Delicious.
Is this strawberry tea?
That's right.
I'm glad you like it.
I sure do.
Um, have you looked around the castle a little?
You don't have to be so nervous.
We have, but just a little bit.
The day after we first arrived, Fuka and I did some exploring.
We even went all the way up to the tower.
The castle is completely surrounded by water, with no land in sight.
You also spent some time looking for the key, but no luck.
I was wondering if they find the key, then...
Oh, how are your rooms?
Mine's really nice.
Yeah, mine is really cool too.
Fuka even has a piano in hers.
I wanted to ask them what their wishes were.
But I couldn't.
To be honest, I wouldn't want them to ask me either.
Coming to the castle is a lot of fun.
Whether I'm hanging out with the others, or by myself.
All of them come here almost every day.
I wonder if they're skipping school just like me.
But no one asks, or even admits to it.
In a way, it's kind of comforting.
Well, they're pretty tasty, don't you think?
Here, take a few more.
You don't have to be shy about it.
Hey, Kokoro!
Why don't you come over here with me?
Right this way.
Don't just stand there.
Have a seat next to me.
These are some of my mom's cookies.
Please go and have as many as you'd like.
I saved the prettiest ones just for you.
Thanks.
You think that move works on the other girls you stratted on?
So, I wanted to ask you.
Do you have a boyfriend or someone you like like that?
Hey, you.
So what?
You decided to switch your focus from Aki to Kokoro now?
Wolf Queen, it's been a while since we last saw you.
Well, come on.
Why are you lazing about?
Shouldn't you be looking for the key?
I don't think it's here.
Maybe you're not looking hard enough.
Well, I guess it doesn't matter if none of you have any wishes.
Urashina's got a wish.
That's for sure.
Kokoro, look deep into my eyes.
Oh, please.
You didn't hear any of that, right?
It's so stupid.
Drop dead.
I went home for a bit to have some lunch, but now I'm back.
So, uh, oh, the others are playing games upstairs.
Hey, since we're great friends and all, Fuca, do you happen to have a nickname you go by?
Maybe Fufu or something like that.
I don't.
My mom just called me clean old Fuca.
Yeah, guess I can see that.
Oh, oh, one more question.
I can't.
Too hard.
I need a break.
Nobody's here.
That's a first.
What's this?
Kokoro.
Ah!
Sorry, didn't mean to scare you.
Mm-hmm.
I didn't know anyone was here.
I'm pretty sure that everyone else is busy over summer break.
Oh, really?
Masamune is with his parents.
Fuca said that she has two weeks of seminar this time during the afternoons.
And Urashino goes to cram school somewhere.
Oh.
Oh, Fuf.
Yo!
Going home?
Uh-huh.
It seems like the others haven't been coming much.
Maybe it's because of summer break?
Uh-huh.
I think they all have summer seminars or something.
Seminars, huh?
What's that?
Eh?
It's like a class where they review what they taught you during first term.
Wow.
Everyone is so studious.
Are you going to?
Huh?
I don't know.
That's a relief.
This is nice.
I feel better now.
Huh?
Don't worry.
I'm not upset.
I think it's great that you're finally going out and getting some fresh air.
I was just surprised to find that you weren't at home when I stopped by.
Why did you come back home?
To spy on me?
No.
Of course not.
My plans changed last minute and I thought we could have lunch together.
I don't want you to monitor me.
Mrs. Kitajima.
You know, the teacher you spoke to at the alternative school, she was asking about you.
She reached out.
She was hoping that the two of you could talk together again.
She knows you can't go back to school, but she knows it's not your fault.
There has to be some reason behind this.
It's what she keeps telling me.
That's why...
Oh, that's your dad.
He's home early.
Hey, why don't we all sit down together?
Summer break, right?
Yeah, but...
Summer break is pretty much over.
Yeah, good point.
Aren't you afraid the teachers will get mad at you?
Everybody's gonna be on edge if you walk into school with your hair dyed like that.
Well, yeah, but I don't really care.
Hmm.
I think it looks good on you.
Maybe I'll try something like that.
Hey, maybe all three of us should try it.
Huh?
Oh.
Although, if I make Fuca do something silly like that, somebody here might get upset.
You already gave Fuca a gift earlier, am I right?
Mommy's special homemade cookies.
Listen up!
Next term, I've decided that I'm gonna go back to school.
I was being polite before, so I didn't say anything till now.
But everyone who comes here, none of you go to school, right?
You can't go to school, am I right?
It's so stupid!
Even you, Aki, you were acting all worried.
What would the teachers think, huh?
What a joke.
Don't talk like that.
Why not?
All of you guys treated me like a joke.
You always do.
You laugh at me, right in my face.
No, that's not true.
Although, maybe it is true.
Like, it was okay to make fun of Urashino.
I'm sick and tired of it!
All of us are the same!
We're losers!
Outsiders!
None of us have any friends!
You're all the same!
And you as well!
You're the same too!
And you, Fuca!
Kokuro, you!
All of you are the same!
Urashino, you need to calm down.
Why don't you tell us what's going on with you first?
What's the reason you stopped going to school?
Go ahead!
What did I...
I didn't.
I still go to school.
Liar!
I'm not lying.
Although, the school isn't in Japan.
I actually go to a boarding school in Hawaii.
Hawaii?
Like, Hawaii, Hawaii?
Uh, that's pretty far away, isn't it?
Yeah.
But that doesn't matter.
Wait a second.
The Wolf Queen said something the first day.
She said the castle's hours were 9 o'clock in the morning till 5 o'clock at night Japan time.
I was wondering why she mentioned the time zone.
Are you, like, rich or something?
Huh?
No, it's actually nothing like that at all.
The school itself was pretty easy to get into, and we mostly focused on training and playing soccer.
Here, you're studying abroad for soccer.
Really?
Hmm.
Yeah.
Why didn't you tell any of us?
You think you're better than us?
Is that what it really is?
Uh, uh, no, of course I don't think that.
At first, I thought everyone else here was studying abroad the same as I was.
But then everybody started talking about afternoons in Japan.
I honestly couldn't tell if you were going to school or not.
I came later because of the time zone.
I don't care.
None of it matters.
I'm going to do what the rest of you couldn't.
I'm going to show you all that I'm different.
I'm going back to school next term.
I'm leaving.
It isn't as bad as it looks, though.
Urashino, want to play?
How about it?
Play with us.
Okay?
Come on.
I can't believe that happened to him, but it is Urashino.
I guess I can't be too surprised about it.
You know what I mean?
He said after he started middle school, his new friends got him to pay for things constantly,
and it looks like things just continue to escalate from there.
I know what it sounds like, but they weren't bullying me or anything like that.
I hadn't seen them all in a while.
Things were kind of awkward, so I thought I should apologize to them.
And I did.
It sounds like they should be the ones apologizing.
According to the teacher, they were all worried about me the whole time I was out.
But when we talked, all they said is that I'm useless if I didn't pay for things.
That's when I snapped and shoved one of them, and they shoved back.
Oh, boy.
I guess this is a safe space for all of us, even Urashino.
I wanted to ask...
Hmm?
Um...
Well, I...
I noticed you haven't come to the castle in a while.
Why's that?
Hmm.
That's true.
What?
I have a boyfriend now.
Huh?
Keep it a secret.
It's been a while.
Are you doing well?
Yeah.
Come in.
I can't stay long, so we can talk right here.
I thought about waiting for your mother so that the three of us could speak together.
But I figured it'd be best if just the two of us talked first.
And your mother and I talk every now and then.
It would be nice to have you start coming to our school at some point, once you're feeling up to it.
You said something to my mother about it not being my fault.
Did you really say that?
It surprised me.
Hmm.
W-why?
Why?
I said it.
Because you're fighting every single day.
Isn't that true?
Can I visit again sometime?
Sure.
This is some of the tea I like to drink.
I thought that you might like to have some.
I hope that you'll take it.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
I'll see you later.
Since all seven of us happened to be here today, I think it's time to talk things over.
What should we do from here?
It's October, so we've only got six months left.
And we still haven't found the key yet.
We've looked pretty thoroughly.
Masamune and I both searched together.
I spent a day searching by myself.
Masamune snuck up on me in the dining room.
You were focused on your search.
That's why you didn't hear me come in.
You waited till we all left.
So that way you could search for the key all by yourself every day.
Except I couldn't find it.
So I think we should work together to look for it.
We may be rivals.
But if we find it, I figure we could just decide whose wish gets granted by drawing straws or rock, paper, scissors or something.
I'm a little surprised to hear this, Aki.
I didn't even know you had a wish.
Or that you were so keen on this, Masamune.
I mean, doesn't everyone have a wish or two that's important to them?
I'm in.
Me too.
But if we're gonna do this, how about we promise one thing?
Even if one of us finds the key, let's not use it until late March.
Good idea!
It would suck to lose this place.
Yeah.
What do you think?
Huh.
Okay then, let's figure out who goes where.
Nope.
Aki did tell us that she searched the kitchen pretty thoroughly.
Even so, we might be able to find something she missed.
Huh?
What's this?
Oh, I was wondering what that cross was for.
I noticed it earlier.
Are you okay?
Your arm hasn't healed yet?
Yeah, but it's feeling a lot better.
Except when I stretch it.
Huh.
Hey, Fuuka.
Before, I said a lot of weird stuff because I was angry.
But I really like it here.
Staying at the castle was fun.
Hmm.
Huh.
So you won't be going back to school then?
No, I won't.
But the other school I go to has a really great teacher.
The alternative school?
The teacher there is always checking in on me and asking me what I want.
When I talk, she really listens.
Wow.
Oh, crap.
Hey!
Time's up, guys!
No luck, huh?
Well, there's nothing else we can do today.
Let's find time to search again.
What marvelous solidarity.
Hi there. We meet again, Little Red Riding Hoods.
Out of nowhere, as usual.
You all seem to be having a lot of fun together.
I had to see it for myself.
I hope this won't be a problem.
We can search for the key together, right?
Yes, cooperate.
It's lovely to see.
One more thing.
I forgot to mention it before.
Huh?
When you find the key, and a wish has been granted,
all your memories of this place will vanish.
What do you mean?
This castle, and all your time spent here, will be forgotten.
You won't remember each other, me, or anything else.
On the other hand, if no one's wishes granted by March 30th,
you'll keep your memories.
And you'll all continue to remember the time you spent here.
The choice is up to you.
Whatever you decide.
To be honest, speaking for myself, I'm fine if I lose these memories.
I'm fine with that.
Because we wouldn't have met otherwise.
You know what I mean?
Aki, does your wish really mean that much to you?
I, uh...
Hmm?
So, uh, there's this girl, Sanada, who has been a big problem for me.
Right when school started, this pretty transfer student named Moe Tojo joined her class.
She lived across the street from me, and we became friends pretty quickly.
Sanada's really popular.
She's not shy.
She's always surrounded by people who want to be her friend.
Even the teachers couldn't help liking her.
What is it?
You know, I hate ugly girls.
Girls like you.
Are you happy now?
Did you really think that Ikeda would ask you out?
Well, I guess you thought wrong.
Seriously, Ikeda would never actually fall for a girl like you.
It's so stupid.
Drop dead.
That boy Ikeda, back in elementary school, he told me once that he had a crush on me.
But, it was just the once.
Then, when we started junior high, Sanada started dating Ikeda.
That wasn't even the worst of it.
Kokoro, are you there?
There wasn't just a couple of people outside my house.
It felt like a whole group.
Come on out!
Yeah, make it quick!
Don't hide!
I know you're in there.
Let's try the backyard.
We can check the window.
You better come out or we'll crash your garden.
What have you been doing in this?
She's too rare to come out.
Kokoro, have a way with us!
You better come out wherever you are.
You shouldn't be eyeing someone else's boyfriend.
Sanada, that has something to say to you.
Don't be such a baby.
It looked open.
She's totally in there.
Get out here, you stupid coward!
Get out here.
Come on, show yourself!
Mom, mom, mom!
That girl, how could she...
Sanada, please don't cry.
Stupid girl came on to her boyfriend.
She deserves what's coming.
I hate you!
Stop hiding!
Open up!
Why aren't you coming out?
I won't forgive you!
Take me all you want.
Don't forgive me.
Because I will never forgive you either.
I panicked.
To be honest, I thought they were really going to kill me.
Before I knew it, the whole house was dark.
And it was all quiet outside.
It wasn't long until my mom came back home.
But I couldn't tell her what happened.
I don't know why.
And because of all that, I eventually stopped going to school.
You're safe.
Okay?
You've been brave for so long.
Hmm.
Well done.
I wanted to tell somebody.
I wanted somebody to listen to me.
I thought if it wasn't for Sanada, everything would be easier.
I wanted to find the key and wish for her to disappear from this world, so we'd never have to see her again.
But I...
I don't want to lose my memories of all of you.
I have no idea what I'm supposed to do.
Despite everything that happened, we continue to look for the key.
Have you tried to work this?
Oh, that.
None of us have been able to figure out what it is.
I think I might know.
Huh?
Then.
Hmm?
Is this a music box?
Hmm.
Hey, what's going on in here?
How's it doing that?
Rion figured out how it works.
It's toy, Morai.
Oh.
This must be an antique music box.
It's lovely.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
She showed up like this.
Aki?
Sorry.
I'm fine, you guys.
Uh, what?
That school uniform.
It's Yuki Shina's.
Hmm.
So you figured it out.
Yeah, it's surprising.
All seven of us go to the same junior high school, Yuki Shina and Minami, Tokyo.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
I got sent to boarding school before entering junior high.
If I stayed, that's the school I would have gone to.
There are a lot of us here.
And we're all not going to our junior high school.
Huh.
Maybe if you talked to each other more, you little red riding hoods would have figured this out a lot sooner.
Oh, well.
You seem to be enjoying all of this.
Oh, no.
I am not one to have such wicked motives in my heart.
Then explain all this.
Just what is it you want from us?
Nothing to speak of.
I don't want anything from you.
This place and the chance to find the key is all that I offer to you, Seven.
Nothing more and nothing less.
They're all here.
We're together in the same town.
It makes me feel better for some reason.
Oh, my gosh.
Up till now, I couldn't tell you.
I wanted to, but I just couldn't.
I had no idea at all.
Look, Mom.
This wasn't just some argument we had.
It was so much worse.
Then we'll fight, okay?
You and I will fight this together.
Kokoro.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I should have noticed.
Thank you.
Kokoro, it's been a while.
You well?
Well, I'm happy we can finally speak.
I've been asking about you.
Mrs. Kitajima.
Wasn't she supposed to be here as well?
This is simply a school issue.
I don't see the need.
I've already spoken with Sanada.
I'm happy to clear up any misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
How's this?
We could set up a meeting between you and Miss Sanada to talk things out.
Hey, look up here.
Hey, Mr. Hark.
We're up here.
You know, Mr. Ida's such a dumbass.
For real.
You know, she's the kind of girl that's easy to misunderstand.
And I know you've been having a tough time yourself, Kokoro.
However, Sanada said she's sorry.
And she's worried about her.
I seriously doubt she's sorry.
And if she really is worried, it's only because a teacher scolded her for what she had done.
What she's scared of is a teacher thinking badly of her.
And nothing else.
Kokoro, I'm not so sure that we've...
Mr. Ida, shouldn't you start by asking Kokoro what happened and getting her side of the story?
If that other girl was able to do so, shouldn't you be doing the same for my daughter?
Yes, of course.
Although, I do believe the two of them should be able to work...
That's quite enough.
The next time you come, I should like the first year's administrator or the principal to accompany you as well.
Is that understood?
Whoa.
That's beautiful.
Homemade? From a girl?
Uh, kinda. My mom.
She makes one every year.
She visits for Christmas.
She's flying back now.
Already? That's quick.
Two nights, three days.
She's pretty busy.
Oh, I see.
Alright, let's dig in already!
Yeah, let's eat!
Hey, why don't we invite the Wolf Queen?
Good idea.
You called?
Every time.
Christmas cake.
My mom makes it every year.
We've got the Christmas version of the Wolf Queen today.
Sure do.
It's really cute.
Hang on. Can you eat with your mask on?
No. I can't eat here.
You can cut me a piece. I'll eat by myself.
I never thought you'd say yes.
Who would have guessed that the Wolf Queen likes cake too?
Hey, I've got something I need to ask you guys.
Do you think you could all come to school for the third term for me?
Even if it is, just for a day or two.
My folks, they want me to transfer to a different junior high.
Even though I thought going to the other school was enough for them.
You go there? To the alternative school? Really?
Yeah. I mean, sometimes.
They've got this one cool teacher there.
Hold on. Which teacher?
A woman?
And is her name Mrs. Kitajima, by chance?
Yeah.
Wow. Really?
Problem is, it isn't exactly a real school.
We don't study all that much.
So private school, then.
Your folks have no faith in public school teachers, right?
Yeah.
My dad is really well connected.
He's gonna set something up for me, so.
My parents and I have talked about it, too.
That somewhere else might work out better, right?
I'm worried.
If I transfer, what if I can't come back to the castle?
Huh?
So I talked to my dad.
I told him I want to go back to Yukishina, at least for the third term.
But you'll just...
Just come for the first day.
That's all I'm asking you to do.
Please.
You don't even have to go to class.
We can meet in the nurse's office.
Or the library.
Maybe it's not a coincidence we all go to the same school.
Maybe we're supposed to look out for each other.
It's okay.
You didn't have to take the day off from work.
Are you sure?
I can go with you.
Mm-mm.
I'll be all right.
Well, I better go.
Please take care.
I didn't come here just for school.
I came here for my friends.
It's Moe.
But why?
Let's go.
Dear Kokoro Anzai, I heard from Mr. Ida that you'll be coming to school tomorrow, and he said I should write you a letter, so here it is.
Miss Anzai, why do you hate me?
All I want to do is meet with you and talk things over.
I guess I can understand if you're still heartbroken over Ai. However, you should know that over the summer, we broke up.
If you still like him, maybe I can do something to help you.
Come on, guys. Please be here.
Miss Anzai?
What's wrong?
What's a Masumune here? He's a second year.
Huh?
Maybe someone named Fuka?
How about Akio Subaru?
Those two or thirty years...
Calm down, Miss Anzai.
What's this about?
And there's a first year.
What does she know?
His name's not that common, so you must know him. Right?
I'm afraid I don't. There's no first year with that name.
What?
I might know the others, if you can tell me their last names.
Last names? I don't know Aki's last name. Or Fuka's.
Kokoro?
Mrs. Kirishima.
What are you doing here?
Your mother told me that you'd be here today, so I thought it would be best if I checked in on you.
Oh, I see.
Looks like you're feeling better.
You were so pale when I got here.
This is yours, right? You were clutching it in your hand.
I'm sorry. I read it without asking.
I don't want it.
I spoke to Mr. Iida about what happened. He was out of line.
I should have spoken to him about your situation from the beginning.
Instead, you've only been hurt more. I'm sorry.
I saw her. Just before, Maui told you I was there. But she ignored me, completely.
No, hello. No, it's good to see you.
She walked right by, and said nothing.
What if it was her? Was she the one who put Sanada's letters in my cubby?
Could it be that Sanada asked her to do it?
After all, she was the one who'd stop at my house every day to drop off school notices.
What if she hates me now? What do I do?
Don't worry.
We know what happened.
That's because somebody stepped forward and told us.
It was Miss Tojo.
Huh?
When she saw you, maybe she was just caught by surprise and didn't know what to say.
But there's one thing you can trust, and it's that your friend is clearly concerned about you.
Is she really? Is that true?
Hmm.
Hey, Rian.
The others haven't shown up yet?
Hmm.
I only just got here.
I had a break during soccer practice, but nobody's here.
Oh, so how'd it go?
Hmm.
Huh.
We couldn't meet up.
I'm not sure why, but no one came.
No Masamune, or the others.
But the really weird thing is, the nurse told me that none of them go to Yukishina.
Huh?
But how?
I don't know.
That's why I came here to ask them about it.
What if everything in this castle, even these mirrors, what if it's not real?
What if all of you don't actually exist?
Just thinking about that scares me.
What?
I'm real, okay?
I'm really here.
That's no lie.
The others, they have to be real, too.
Something must have kept them away.
This castle, along with the fact that we all met here, I think it has to mean something.
Also, we're all dealing with stuff that can't be random.
Does that mean you are, too, Rian?
Well.
So if you end up finding the key, what is it that you would want to wish for?
What I'd wish for?
It's my sister.
I'd wish for her to come back.
Huh?
The year I started elementary school, she got sick and died.
My sis...
Sorry.
I know stuff like this is hard to hear.
Mm-mm.
I wasn't going to tell anyone.
Truth is, for a while I was set on finding the key.
But now I'm not so sure.
Compared to him?
My wish is so petty.
I should probably get back.
Oh.
I should go, too.
My mom is waiting for me.
It feels like a fake-out.
Huh?
The Wolf Queen.
Are we really red riding hoods to her?
Huh?
Kokoro, why didn't you show up?
I did.
I was the only one who did show up.
Huh.
That's what the others said.
Right, Fuca?
I swear to you I was there.
So was I.
Me, too.
We didn't meet, did we?
Well, the nurse told me that there were no firsters at school named Kokoro.
I asked, too.
I thought she might know you since your name's so unusual.
But she didn't.
Ugh.
What is going on?
There's more.
I checked in on the class that Masamune is supposed to be in.
Except they told me that there was nobody there with that name.
Um, Masamune's not here yet?
We waited for Masamune to arrive.
We waited the next day.
And the day after.
But he didn't come.
And just as we thought he'd never come back, he finally showed up.
There's only one explanation.
Each of us is an inhabitant of a different parallel world.
A different parallel world?
Like, the ones that pop up a lot in science fiction?
Some video games are about that.
Yeah.
So basically, these worlds each have a different yukashina junior high, and we're all going to our own schools.
We may be in the same room now, but we're from other worlds.
I'll show you.
The opinion.
Besides, if you think this means we have some entrance aboard a stuk.
Some sort of link to where it comes from are like its branches.
Since they all grow from the same trunk, they're a lot alike, but slightly different ultimately.
Which is why Subaru's not in my world.
Or why Kokoro and Fuko or Enaki's.
Gate World. You've never heard of it?
Professor Nagahisa's new game.
It's selling like crazy.
I have a friend who knows him.
They even let me test out the new game, so...
Nagahisa?
Professor Nagahisa's iptoplet.
He's the genius game director over at Unison.
Man, really?
You guys don't even know the basics.
I've heard of that one. G-World.
It was such a huge hit.
They made it a movie.
No, they didn't.
They didn't?
Hey, I know you're listening.
Come on out, Wolf Queen.
After all, one truth prevails, so they say.
Who says that?
What is with all the racket?
Come on, now you heard me.
Am I right or what?
Not at all.
Huh?
All this time, and the only thing you could come up with
is some half-baked video game premise.
You should hit the reset button.
But then, how come our realities are slightly different from each other?
And we can't meet up in the outside world.
So, parallel worlds is the only answer, right?
What makes you think you can't meet?
I never said that.
Huh?
So we can meet?
Work it out for yourselves already.
Think!
I gave you a hint at the start of all this.
I also left you more than enough clues about the key.
About the key?
Actually, I found something under my bed.
It's some sort of cross symbol.
What does it mean?
There's something like that under my desk, too.
I just thought it was some sort of emblem.
There's one in the bath.
It stuck out since there's no running water.
I checked and saw it there.
I saw one in the oven the other day.
There's another one in the dining room cabinet, as well.
You're right.
I saw one.
It's inside the closet in my room.
Sick so far.
But there could be even more of them.
Are these also hints?
Think about it.
This castle and its mysteries are all part of the mission you've been given.
Forget finding the key and stay until the end.
Or find the key.
And grant your wish.
You're free to choose.
You're fine.
Still no sign of it, the key.
And we're quickly running out of time.
Looks like I can only play video games here for another two weeks.
You know, if it wasn't for you showing me, I never would have realized how cool video games can be.
I'm amazed at how advanced they are now. It's crazy.
You finish them faster than me. RPGs, fighting games, it doesn't matter.
That's just not fair at all.
Well, it really made me interested in computers. I want to study them properly. So I decided to go back.
About a month ago, I took an entrance exam. I wanted to get into a part-time tech school and I got accepted.
You studied to get into a tech school?
Yeah, more or less.
I had no idea.
Looks like I'll be switching schools.
Whoa, really?
My dad was able to find me a pretty decent private school. I took the entrance exam. Got in yesterday.
Good for you.
Actually, I'll probably transfer schools too.
While my dad is to stay in Japan for work, he and mom talked. And we'll be looking at schools overseas.
You're studying abroad. That's amazing.
I'm torn. I still don't know what I'm going to do. My parents are telling me I should transfer too. But I just can't decide.
Fuuka's been playing the piano a lot more often lately.
I know. She mentioned to me that she's enjoying it a lot more too.
I wonder if she's gonna stick with it and keep playing piano.
Who knows? Maybe she will.
As for me, I'll repeat.
Hmm?
Everybody says that I should do the year all over again.
I didn't do any studying. No surprise there.
So sorry I got here late.
Oh, it's alright.
Kokoda wanted to get a burger. So we came early.
How are you? Is this okay?
I thought meeting somewhere more lively might be a nice change of pace.
Tell me if it's too much.
As for your future school plans, I've already met with your mom a couple of times.
I also had a chance to speak with your dad.
You talked with my dad?
Mm-hmm.
We wanted to discuss your options and to figure out what would be the best path for you.
You could switch to another school. It would be in an adjacent district nearby.
Or you could stay at Yukishina and then switch into a different class than Sanada.
I could do that?
Yes.
I've spoken to all of the school administrators and they've all said they've made it their top priority.
And will they also be doing something about Sanada's friends?
Ah. You're referring to Toyosaka and Maeda from your class, correct?
Oh, along with Nakayama, of course.
They'll all be switching classes as well.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, and we'll also be getting you a new homeroom teacher if we can.
And, um, what about Moe Tojo?
Miss Tojo will be transferring schools again.
What?
You know that her dad's a college professor, right?
I heard that he'll be teaching at a college in Nagoya starting in April.
Mm-hmm.
We can visit schools in the neighboring districts.
Mm.
Although, if you don't want to, there's no need to go back to junior high.
Huh?
Your mom and I are both of the opinion that school isn't necessarily the answer, and you don't have to go.
You could just attend the classroom of the heart. Or other options.
Hm.
You are not alone.
We'll work together to figure out what's best for you.
Okay.
So cute.
Want one?
Yeah.
Hey, let's go to the convenience store.
I want to buy snacks.
Of course.
Tomorrow will be our last day.
I'm all prepped for the farewell party.
This is what I think.
There have been others who couldn't go to school like me.
And just like me, they met the Wolf Queen and spent time at the castle.
No one ever finds out about it because, when their wishes are granted, all their memories of that place fade away.
Whether my wish gets granted or not, I'm grateful the castle in the mirror exists.
Truly grateful.
Can I come in and clean?
But Mom, what about work?
Someone's coming by.
They'll be cleaning our AC system.
I figured I'd pop into work later in the afternoon.
Can I come in?
Let me do it.
I'm sorry.
They'll be cleaning our AC system.
I figured I'd pop into work later in the afternoon.
Can I come in?
Let me do it.
Do you want to come over?
Good thing I bought two of these.
Which would you like?
Um, let's see.
Let's see.
This one.
I, uh, wanted to thank you for writing that letter.
By the way, is it true?
You're transferring schools?
Hmm.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
When I saw you that day, at school by the cubbies.
I wanted to say something, but then couldn't.
Things were still awkward for me.
Awkward?
Recently, Sonata's group had turned on me.
That's why, if they had found out I talked to you, they might have done something to you, too.
But, what happened?
I'm not completely sure.
For some reason, they all thought I looked down on them, and they really didn't like that.
Huh.
They said I tried to steal Nakayama's boyfriend, that I'm a guy stealer, and also a homewrecker.
I had enough.
I did look down on them all.
Huh.
They're so shallow.
All they care about, all they ever talk about is boy stuff.
None of them care about school, and they're all immature.
They'll be the same in 10-20 years.
Still living their shallow lives.
Whoa, Molly.
What?
I'm surprised.
I don't think that I've ever heard you talk like that before.
Too harsh?
Not at all.
I'm glad.
I guess, since now I'm the primary target of their hatred instead of you, they'll probably start acting friendly with you if you come back.
That way, I'll feel isolated.
But that's... so mean.
That's just how they are.
That's so stupid.
I mean, it's only school, right?
It's only school?
Don't let them win, Kokoro.
Huh?
Kids like those girls are everywhere.
There might even be some at my next school as well.
But when something happens, from now on, I'll speak out.
I think you should do the same.
Yeah.
If someone's being hurt by others, I want to try and help if I can.
Hang on.
Hmm?
This picture of a wolf...
It's the wolf and the seven little goats.
Seven goats?
I'm so sorry.
I promise I'll give it right back.
It's quite okay.
I'm not moving for another two days.
Thank you.
Bye!
Oh no.
Why?
How did...
Wolf Queen!
Tell me!
What's going on over there?
Answer me!
Huh?
Oh no.
Why?
How did...
Wolf Queen!
Tell me!
What's going on over there?
Answer me!
Huh?
Kokoro.
What happened to you guys?
What's going on?
It's Aki.
She's broken the rule.
Huh?
It was past five, but she didn't leave the castle.
A giant wolf ate her.
Ah.
And it's coming to eat us too.
Huh?
It's going to eat us too.
What's going on?
It's Aki.
She's broken the rule.
Huh?
It was past five, but she didn't leave the castle.
A giant wolf ate her.
Huh?
And it's coming to eat us too.
Oh, no.
We share our fate.
We ran home, but we instantly got sucked back in.
And now we can't go back. We're trapped.
What is it? What's wrong?
Guys, no, please wait!
Guru, listen. Find the key and save Aki.
I found this! I think it might be a clue.
Aki, why? Why'd you go and break the one rule?
Don't worry. You'll be all right.
I'll save you. And the others.
I'll make sure of it.
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
The first little goat hit under the table.
Vuka.
The second hit under the bed.
The third inside the closet.
The fourth hit inside the kitchen stove.
The fifth inside the cupboard.
The sixth under the wash tub.
Wolf queen.
Can you hear me?
As for the hiding place of the seventh little goat, no one would ever find it.
Never reach it.
While the other six little goats were busy hiding, the last little goat was able to leap into it.
It has to be there.
That's where the wishing key is hidden.
Right, wolf queen?
The fifth one.
Thank you.
There's no way they wouldn't have come.
I know how you must feel, but there has to be a reason your friends couldn't make it today.
Thank you.
For real.
Why'd you show up?
Look at him.
He's peaking out.
Looks like it's a migratory bird.
I wonder if I can read you on his friends.
Haruka.
Hey, Mom.
Oh, Mrs. Kirajima, you came here too.
Your friends haven't come yet.
Have you been waiting long?
Hmm.
Come now, Subaru.
Hurry up indeed already.
I mean, seriously.
Look at his damn hair.
Man.
Both you boys are just as hopeless as your father.
Incredible.
Your daughter's a prodigy.
Oh.
Mrs. Kirajima, Lucca Saro as well.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Aki, is something wrong?
The piano. Do you like it?
Like it? It's more... I guess I love it after all.
Wow. You're studying a lot, aren't you?
Knock, knock, knock. It's your mother, dears.
You're lying. You're the wolf.
No, I'm your mother. Your voice sounds nothing like I'm others.
Listen, Rian. If I pass on and go to heaven, I'll do something for you.
If you tell me one of your wishes, I can ask God to grant it when we meet.
My wish is to go to school with you, sis.
Huh? But you'll be going to elementary school, and I'll be starting junior high.
Then you'll have to wait for me.
Rian, thank you.
I'd really like it if we had the chance to go to school together.
You're lucky. You're so healthy. You know that?
Grandma, this is Atsushi.
He's my boyfriend.
Ha!
What?
Atsushi, please help me!
A-G-L-P-4-3-7-9... come on, work!
Who are you calling?
Sneaky brat?
Are you all right?
But how did you... you used my mom's mirror?
It was urgent.
Aki, what's wrong?
Nobody's coming.
I don't fit in here at school, and I can't go home either.
What am I supposed to do?
If I had the key, I'd wish... I'd wish that he'd die.
I don't have anywhere left to go.
I don't let her go back.
She's not here.
Aki, where are you?
Aki?
Aki!
We're out of time!
Let's go.
We have to leave now or else.
What the... why?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Oh!
Kokoro, listen!
Find the key and save Aki!
The key, it has to...
You saw it?
Wolf Queen, you're here!
Where's Aki and the others?
They were eaten.
They shared the same fate.
What happened to them is out of my control.
Once a rule is broken, there is nothing that can stop what's coming.
This place is built on that condition.
Every action comes with a price.
It's not fair.
Because you weren't in the castle then, it did not apply to you.
Your life was spared.
Each of the symbols you have gathered are their grave markers.
That's why you were able to see fragments of their memories.
How you use the keys up to you.
It's your choice.
We can meet again.
There's a way, right?
That decision is now in your hands.
You will find Aki in the wishing room.
I'm not going to die.
You can't see it.
What's the plan for you on out there?
Because I had to airport within two,every there's and a little,
where you can take the gas off and tap into your eyes.
Theryono's appropriate is visible.
My wish is for Aki to be saved from her fate until the fact that she broke the rules.
Please!
Aki, don't run, come back this way!
We can meet again.
We'll try hard, grow up, and help each other.
So please, you've got to live!
Come find me, in the future.
Years from now, I live in a time after you've grown up.
We all come from different times.
Each one of us is a student at Yukishina Junior High, but in our own year.
Kokoro, I'm so sorry.
It's okay, none of that matters now!
Aki!
You're alright!
Aki, come back to us!
Everyone here is waiting for you!
Come on, Aki!
You're gonna be okay.
You're out here!
Aki!
Here we go!
Hold!
Now!
Aki!
Get out!
I'm really sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Hucky.
You're okay.
I'm so glad.
Bravo, everyone.
Wolf Queen.
Whoa.
If that's true, Subaru and Urashino are 42 years apart.
They are.
I can't believe you're from 2027.
I mean, it's like you're from the world of tomorrow.
What year were you born in?
2013.
So that means you're eight years younger than me.
Um, yeah, I am.
So it happens even in your time.
They're still there.
Kids just like us.
But you know, if they have this castle, they can help each other.
Even if they forget it all.
Interesting.
It looks like we're all seven years apart.
You're right.
Hang on.
What about here?
There's a 14-year gap between you and Rion and me.
I wonder why.
The year would be 1999.
Maybe there was supposed to be someone else.
But for some reason, they couldn't make it.
Mm-mm.
I don't think so.
In the story, there's only seven little goats.
And we're seven years apart.
It kind of feels to me like the number seven means something.
Anyone looking at us would just see regular junior high kids.
But some of us are from the far future.
And some are from the past.
It feels kind of weird.
It honestly makes me wonder how we never realized it before.
Although, Kokoro and Rion are from the same year.
Mm.
Except that Rion wasn't a student at Yukishina Junior High.
Maybe it's because that's where I really wanted to go to school.
I was hoping to stay in Japan and make friends there.
Maybe that's the reason.
And to meet you, Kokoro.
Hmm.
Perhaps.
But we're all different ages.
I don't think we'd ever recognize each other.
Not that it matters.
We're going to be losing our memories anyway.
Hmm.
You've finally stopped talking.
So does that mean it's time?
We really can't stay.
Unfortunately, the castle will be closed beginning today.
It will be as if nothing had happened.
Go and collect your things.
Time's up, huh?
Gotta hurry.
My sheet music and textbooks.
My makeup set.
Nagahisa sip tuplets game.
Big sis.
The castle was set to close tomorrow, which is the anniversary of your death.
You know, if I had the key, I was planning on wishing that you'd come back to us.
In all this, it looks just like it.
Your castle dollhouse.
Huh?
The one missing from 1999 is you, isn't it?
You were supposed to go to Yukishina, but couldn't.
At first, I was thinking that my late sister had somehow come back to see me.
But now I know.
You come here directly from your hospital room.
Right now, as I'm talking to you, you're lying in your bed next to six-year-old me.
You've been spending your last year with all of us here.
This dollhouse was a home.
One that you created.
The reason that you look like a little girl is because that's when you were healthy.
Back when you were six or seven years old.
I'm right, aren't I?
Big sis.
It's time.
Subaru, Nagehisa.
Akiko Inoue.
Rian Mizumori.
Kokura Anzai.
Fuka Hasegawa.
Haruka Urashino.
Earth, Masamune.
What?
So Masamune is your last name?
Earth?
Huh.
That's your name?
I don't want to hear it, Gen Xer.
And Urashino's first name is Haruka.
I know it makes me sound like I'm a girl, but I have to say I've gotten to like it.
Subaru.
As in the Seven Sisters.
The Pleiades.
Hey, Fuka.
If we ever meet again in the outside world...
We wouldn't know each other if we did meet.
Uh, even so, I know I'll fall in love with you at first sight.
And so...
Hmm.
You know, I'm gonna make video games.
Huh?
So go and brag about me.
Hmm.
Kokura, thank you for saving me.
Aki, I...
It's okay.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'll be there 14 years in your future.
Come and see me.
Of course, I will.
Hmm.
Take care.
See you guys.
Bye.
See ya.
I hope someday we'll get to meet again.
Hmm.
Bye.
Big sis, I swear.
I'm gonna make things work.
I'll speak up for myself and what I want to do.
And for the things I don't want to do.
Including Tamang.
Hmm.
If it isn't too much to ask, could you grant me one favor?
I want to remember all this.
Everyone I've met here.
Including you, Wolf Queen.
Hmm.
I guess not.
I'll see what I can do.
Huh.
Thank you.
Big Sis, I know you'll be there when I go to school.
We'll be going to school together.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Good afternoon, Miss Inoue.
Sorry, force of habit.
Or rather, Mrs. Akiko Kirajima.
Oh, is that a new name tag?
Yeah, how's it look?
It's lovely. Your ring, that is.
My ring?
It's nice to meet you.
You must be Kokuro.
My name is Mrs. Kirajima.
May I sit down?
According to our records, you're currently attending Yukishina Junior High School. Is that right?
Yes.
I went there for Junior High, too.
You'll be fine.
Huh?
You'll be just fine.
So keep on growing, Kokuro.
Any requests for dinner tonight?
How about cabbage rolls?
Cabbage rolls.
Okay, got it.
Don't push yourself too hard.
If it's too much, just come home.
Bye.
Take care, honey.
Hey!
Good morning.
We're in the same class.
Isn't that right?
My name's Mizumori.
Riyan Mizumori.
Come on.
Good morning.
Bye.
Good.
Good morning.
Good night.
Thank you.